Guide to the Casey Recordings, 1944-1985 CASEY.2001
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Test Pressings, 1947-1948; IX.
  - [?] No. 27; Mozart, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0010)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Mozart's No. 27[?]. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - Italian Symphony; Mendelssohn, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0011)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes an Italian Symphony. Original sleeve indicates "Mendelssohn's Italian." Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Italian Symphony; Mendelssohn, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0012)
  - Zaza, 1947 (Record CAS TST 0013)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Zaza. Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Slavonic Dance [?]; Dvorak [?]], 1947 (Record CAS TST 0014)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Slavonic Dance by Dvorak. Original sleeve indicates "Dvorak Slavonic Dance Pops" and original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Surry with the Fringe on Top from Oklahoma! (Record CAS TST 0015)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Surry with the Fringe on Top from Oklahoma! The label is handwritten.
  - Oh What a Beautiful Morning from Oklahoma! (Record CAS TST 0016)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Oh What a Beautiful Morning from Oklahoma! The label is handwritten.
  - ?? No. 27; Mozart (Record CAS TST 0017)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Mozart's No. 27[?] The handwritten label is mostly illegible.
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0018)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes unknown content. This album appears to be a duplicate of RC 0422.
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0019)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes unknown content. Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0020)
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0021)
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0022)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes unknown content. Original sleeve inside new sleeve. This album possibly includes Beethoven sonata as the issue number is close to RC 0414.
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0023)
  - Beethoven Piano Sonata [?], 1948 (Record CAS TST 0024)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Beethoven Piano Sonata[?] Original sleeve indicates Beethoven piano sonata. Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Mazurka in F Minor, Op. 7, No. 3 (Record CAS TST 0025)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Mazurka in F Minor, Op. 7, No. 3. The label is handwritten.
  - Beecham [?]; [illegible], 1948 (Record CAS TST 0026)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes unknown content performed by Beecham[?] Original sleeve inside new sleeve. The title is illegible.
  - Concerto; Brahms (Record CAS TST 0027)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes a Concerto by Brahms. The writing on the label is somewhat illegible.
  - Italian Symphony; Mendelssohn, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0028)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Italian Symphony by Mendelssohn. Original sleeve indicates "Mendelssohn's Italian." Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Sonata Op. 12, No. 1; Beethoven, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0029)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Sonata Op. 12, No. 1 by Beethoven. Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Mehne [?]; Beethoven [?], 1948 (Record CAS TST 0030)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes unknown content by Beethoven[?] Original sleeve indicates "Beethoven." Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - A Sonata in G Minor [?]; Rachmaninoff, 1947 (Record CAS TST 0031)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes a Sonata in G Minor [?] by Rachmaninoff. Original sleeve indicates "Kapell [and Kurty?]." The writing is illegible. Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Sonata Op. 12, No. 2; Beethoven, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0032)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Sonata Op. 12, No. 2 by Beethoven. Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - Ernestine Schumann-Heink sings Brindisi from Donizetti's opera Lucrezia Borgia (recorded in 1906) and Leggiero Invisible by Ardita (recorded in 1907), 1947 (Record CAS TST 0033)
    This album consists of 2 discs. Disc 1 is a one-sided test pressing that includes Sinfonia [?] by Bach. Disc 2 side (A) includes Brindisi by Donizetti. Side (B) includes Leggiero Invisible by Ardita. Disc 2 is in a gold cover. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - Unknown, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0034)
  - First Piano Quartet [?], 1948 (Record CAS TST 0035)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes a First Piano Quartet [?] Original sleeve indicates "First Piano Quartet." Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Merrill, 1948 (Record Cas TST 0036)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes unknown content performed by Merrill. Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - G Minor Sonata [?]; Rachmaninoff [?], 1947 (Record Cas TST 0036)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes G Minor Sonata [?] by Rachmaninoff [?] The album has the same designation as the Merrill album. Original sleeve indicates "Kappel + [Kurtz?] Rach. G minor [?] Sonata. Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - G Minor Sonata [?]; Rachmaninoff [?], 1947 (Record CAS TST 0037)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes G Minor Sonata [?] by Rachmaninoff [?] Original sleeve indicates "Kappel + [Kurtz?] Rach. G minor [?] Sonata. Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - G Minor Sonata [?]; Rachmaninoff [?], 1947 (Record CAS TST 0038)
  - G Minor Sonata [?]; Rachmaninoff [?], 1947 (Record CAS TST 0039)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes G Minor Sonata [?] by Rachmaninoff [?] Original sleeve indicates "Kappel + [Kurtz? R?] Rach. G minor [?] Sonata. Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - Sinfonia [?]; Bach, 1948 (Record CAS TST 0040)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Sinfonia [?] by Bach. Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Toccata; Rachmaninoff [?], 1947 (Record CAS TST 0041)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Toccata by Rachmaninoff [?] Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - G Minor Sonata [?]; Rachmaninoff [?], 1947 (Record CAS TST 0042)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes G Minor Sonata [?] by Rachmaninoff [?] The record is cracked and the original sleeve indicates "K and K Rach-G Min. Son." [?] Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Italian Symphony [?]; Mendelssohn [?], 1948 (Record CAS TST 0043)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes Italian Symphony [?] by Mendelssohn [?] Original sleeve indicates "Mendelssohn's Ital." Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - G Minor Sonata [?]; Rachmaninoff [?], 1947 (Record CAS TST 0044)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes G Minor Sonata [?] by Rachmaninoff [?] Original sleeve indicates "K and K Rach-G Min. Son." [?] Original sleeve inside new sleeve.
  - Italian Symphony [?]; Mendelssohn [?], 1948 (Record CAS TST 0045)
  - [?] Variation on the aria La Gicondanza [?] (Record CAS TST 0046)
    This album is a one-sided test pressing that includes [?] Variation on the aria La Gicondanza [?] Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - Horowitz, Vladimir (piano), 1948 (Record CAS TST 0047)
    This albuim is a one-sided test pressing with unknown content performed by Horowitz, Vladimir (piano). Original sleeve inside new sleeve. Writing is somewhat illegible.
  - 10" 80 rpm, no label (Record 10" 80 rpm, no label)
    This album is a 10" 80 rpm disc with no label and unknown contents.
- Classical, 1945-1948, 1962, 1965, 1967, 1971-1973, 1975, 1980; II.
  This series consists of 95 albums. These albums represent the bulk of this collection and showcase the range of classical recordings and artists from the 1940's as captured by RCA Victor.
  - J. S. Bach Concerto in D Minor for Two Violins and Orchestra (Record CAS CLA 0001)
    This album consists of 2 discs with two side each. Disc 1 side (A) includes I: Vivace. Side (B) includes III: Allegro.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes II: Largo ma non tanto (Part 1). Side (B) includes II: Largo ma non tanto (conc.). Also included are program notes by Hall, David on inside of cover. Album includes an 8x10 BW photo of Heifitz taped inside.
  - Bach: Fantasia and Fugue in G Minor (Transcribed by Dimitri Mitropoulos) (Record CAS CLA 0002)
    This album consists of 2 discs with 2 sides each. Dsic 1 side (A) includes Fantasia (Part 1). Side (B) includes Choral Prelude: Wir Glauben All' An.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Fantasia (conc.). Side (B) includes Fugue. Also included are notes inside cover.
  - Johann Sebastian Bach Goldberg Variations, Wanda Landowska, Harpsichord. An RCA Victor Record-Story, 1945 (Record CAS CLA 0003)
    This album consists of 6 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Aria (Sarabande); Var. No. 1. Side (B) includes Var. Nos. 29 and 30; Aria (Sarabande).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Var. Nos. 2, 3, 4 and 5. Side (B) includes Var. Nos. 26, 27, and 28.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Var. Nos. 6, 7, 8 and 9. Side (B) includes Var. No. 25.
    Disc 4 side (A) includes Var. Nos. 10, 11 and 12. Side (B) includes Var. Nos. 23 and 24.
    Disc 5 side (A) includes Var. Nos. 13 and 14. Side (B) includes Var. Nos. 21 and 22. Disc 6 side (A) includes Var. Nos. 15 and 16. Side (B) includes Var. Nos. 17, 18, 19 and 20. The album also includes attached booklet with program notes.
  - J. S. Bach Magnificat (Record CAS CLA 0004)
    This album consists of 5 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Magnificat anima mea Dominum. Side (B) includes (A) 11. Sicut locutus est ad patres nostras (B) 12. Gloria Patria, gloria Filio.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 2. Et exutavit spiritus meus in Deo salutari meo. Side (B) includes 10. Suscepit Israel puerum suum recordatus misericordiae suae.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes (A) 3. Quia respexit humilatatem ancillae suae; ecce enim ex hoc beatam me dicent... (B) 4. …Omnes generationes. Side (B) includes 9. Esurientes implevit bonis et divites dimisit inanes.
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 5. Quia fecit mihi magna qui potens est, et sanctum namum eius. Side (B) includes 8. Deposuit potentes de sede et exaltavit humiles.
    Disc 5 side (A) includes 6. Et misericordia eius a progrenis in progenies timentibus eum. Side (B) includes 7. Fecit potentiam in brachia suo. Album also includes program notes by Hall, David.
  - Johann Sebastian Bach Mass in B Minor, Vol. 1 (Record CAS CLA 0005)
    This album consists of 9 discis with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Kyrie: No. 1: Kyrie eleison (Part 1). Side (B) includes Gloria: No. 11: Cum sancto spiritu. Disc 2 side (A) includes Kyrie: No. 1: Kyrie eleison (Part 2). Side (B) includes Gloria: No. 10: Quoniam tu solis sanctus (conc.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Kyrie: No. 1: Kyrie eleison (conc.). Side (B) includes Gloria: No. 10: Quoniam tu solis sanctus.
    Disc 4 side (A) includes Kyrie: No. 2: Christe eleison (Part 1). Side (B) includes Gloria: No. 9: Qui sedes ad dextram Patris.
    Disc 5 side (A) includes Kyrie: No. 2: Christe eleison (conc.). Side (B) includes Gloria: No. 8: Qui tollis peccata mundi.
    Disc 6 side (A) includes Kyrie: No. 3: Kyrie eleison. Side (B) includes Gloria: No. 7: Domine Deus (conc.).
    Disc 7 side (A) includes Gloria: No. 4: Gloria in excelsis Deo (Part 1). Side (B) includes Gloria: No. 7: Domine Deus (Part 1).
    Disc 8 side (A) includes Gloria: No. 4: Gloria in excelsis Deo (conc.). Side (B) includes Gloria: No. 6: Gratias agimus tibi.
    Disc 9 side (A) includes Gloria: No. 5: Laudamus Te (Part 1). Side (B) includes Gloria: No. 5: Laudamus Te (conc.). Album also Includes program notes, text, and translation on inside cover. Also includes WRONG booklet to another recording, with program notes.
  - Johann Sebastian Bach Mass in B Minor, Vol. 2 (Record CAS CLA 0006)
    This album consists of 8 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Credo: No. 12: Credo in unum Deum. Side (B) includes Agnus Dei: No. 24: Dona nobis pacem.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Credo: No. 13: Patrem omnipotentem. Side (B) includes Agnus Dei: No. 23: Agnus Dei.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes Credo: No. 14: Et in unum Dominum. Side (B) includes Sanctus et Benedictus: No. 22: Benedictus.
    Disc 4 side (A) includes Credo: No. 15: Et incarnatus est. Side (B) includes Sanctus et Benedictus: No. 21: Osanna in exelsis.
    Disc 5 side (A) includes Credo: No. 16: Crucifixus etiam pro nobis. Side (B) includes Sanctus et Benedictus: No. 20: Sanctus, Sanctus, Sanctus (conc.).
    Disc 6 side (A) includes Credo: No. 17: Et resurrexit. Side (B) includes Sanctus et Benedictus: No. 20: Sanctus, Sanctus, Sanctus (Part 1).
    Disc 7 side (A) includes Credo: No. 18: Et in Spiritum Sanctum (Part 1). Side (B) includes Credo: No. 19: Confiteor (conc.).
    Disc 8 side (A) includes Credo: No. 18: Et in Spiritum Sanctum (conc.). Side (B) includes Credo: No. 19: Confiteor (Part 1). Album also includes text and translation on inside cover.
  - Bach: Transcriptions for Orchestra (Record CAS CLA 0007)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes Sonata in E Flat Major for Pedal Clavier: First Movement. Side (B) includes Adoramus Te.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Ich ruf' zu dir, Herr Jesu Christ (chorale prelude). Side (B) includes Prelude and Fugue in E Minor.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes No. 58 Es ist Vollbracht (Part 1). Side (B) includes No. 58 Es ist Vollbracht (conc.). Disc 2 is a Duplicate of RC 0317-0318. All have notes inside cover.
  - No. 3 of Acht kleine Praeludium und Fugen, for Organ (Record CAS CLA 0008)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Ich ruf' zu dir, Herr Jesu Christ (chorale prelude). Side (B) includes Prelude and Fugue in E Minor. Album also Includes notes on inside cover. It is missing record 1 and 3.
  - Beethoven Concert in D Major for Violin and Orchestera, Op. 61. Musical Masterpiece Series (Record CAS CLA 0009)
    This album consists of 5 discs, 4 of which have 2 sides each. Disc 5 has only 1 side. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Allegro ma non troppo (Part 1). Side (B) includes 2. Larghetto (Part 1).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 1. Allegro ma non troppo (Part 2). Side (B) includes 2. Larghetto (conc.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes 1. Allegro ma non troppo (Part 3). Side (B) includes 3. Rondo (Allegro) (Part 1).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 1. Allegro ma non troppo (Part 4). Side (B) includes 3. Rondo (Allegro) (conc.).
    Disc 5 includes 1. Allegro ma non troppo (conc.). Album also includes booklet with program notes by Veinus, A.
  - Rasoumovsky, No. 1: Beethoven Quartet No. 7, in F., Op. 59, No. 1 (Record CAS CLA 0010)
    This album consists of 5 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Allegro (Part 1). Side (B) includes 2. Minuet.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 1. Allegro (Part 2). Side (B) includes 4. Finale; Theme Russe (conc.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes 1. Allegro (conc.). Side (B) includes 3. Adagio Molto (conc.).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 2. Allegretto vivace (Part 1). Side (B) includes 3. Adagio Molto (Part 2).
    Disc 5 side (A) includes 2. Allegretto vivace (conc.). Side (B) includes 3. Adagio Molto (Part 1). Album also includes program notes by Hall, David on inside of cover. Album needs glue.
  - Rasoumovsky No. 2: Beethoven Quartet No. 8, in E Minor, Op. 59, No. 2 (Record CAS CLA 0011)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Allegro (Part 1). Side (B) includes 4. Presto (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 1. Allegro (conc.). Side (B) includes 3. Allegretto (conc.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes 2. Molto Adagio (Part 1). Side (B) includes 3. Allegretto (Part 1).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 2. Molto Adagio (Part 2). Side (B) includes 2. Molto Adagio (conc.). Album also includes program notes by Hall, David inside cover.
  - Rasoumovsky, No. 3: Beethoven Quartet No. 9, in C., Op. 59, No. 3 (Record CAS CLA 0012)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Andante con moto; Allegro vivace (Part 1). Side (B) includes 3. Menuetto.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 1. Allegro vivace (conc.). Side (B) includes 4. Allegro molto (conc.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes 2. Andante con moto quasi allegretto (Part 1). Side (B) includes 4. Allegro molto (Part 1).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 2. Andante con moto quasi allegretto (conc.). Side (B) includes 3. Menuetto grazioso; Coda. Album also includes program notes by Hall, David inside cover.
  - Sonata in F Minor, Op. 57: "Appassionata"; Sonata in E-Flat, Op. 31, no. 3 (Record CAS CLA 0013)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes 1. Allegro Assai. Side (B) includes 3. Minuetto. This album is also part of larger set. Original sleeve is in new sleeve.
  - World's Greatest Music: Beethoven: Symphony No. 5 in C Minor. (Op. 67). In Eight Parts. (Record CAS CLA 0014)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Beethoven: Symphony No. 5 in C Minor. (Op. 67). First movement, part 1. Side (B) includes Beethoven: Symphony No. 5 in C Minor. (Op. 67). First movement, part 2. This album is also missing its cover, and three other records which are part of the set.
  - Beethoven Symphony No. 5 in C Minor, Op. 67 (Record CAS CLA 0015)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes 1. Allegro Con Brio (Part 1). Side (B) includes 1. Allegro Con Brio (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes 2. Andante con moto (Part 1). Side (B) includes 2. Andante con moto (Part 2).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes (A) 2. Andante con moto (conc.) (B) 3. Scherzo: Allegro vivace (Part 1). Side (B) includes (B) 3. Scherzo: Allegro vivace (conc.) (B) 4. Finale: Allegro (Part 1).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 4. Finale: Allegro (Part 2). Side (B) includes 4. Finale: Allegro (conc.). Album also includes booklet with program notes.
  - Jeanne Gerville-Réache sings Habanera from Bizet's Opera Carmen (recorded in 1910) and Chanson du Tigre from Massé's Opera Paul et Virginie, 1947 (Record CAS CLA 0016)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes Habanera. Side (B) includes Chanson du Tigre. The album is in gold cover.
  - Johannes Brahms Alto RhapsodyProgram notes, text and translation inside cover. (Record CAS CLA 0017)
    This album consists of 2 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A)includes Alto Rhapsody, Op. 53 (After Goethe's "Harzreise in Winter"): Part 1. Side (B) includes Alto Rhapsody, Op. 53 (After Goethe's "Harzreise in Winter"): Conc.
    Disc 2 side (A) includes Alto Rhapsody, Op. 53 (After Goethe's "Harzreise in Winter"): Part 2. Side (B) includes Alto Rhapsody, Op. 53 (After Goethe's "Harzreise in Winter"): Part 3. Album also includes program notes, text and translation inside cover.
  - Brahms. Double Concerto in A Minor for Violin, Cello and Orchestra (Record CAS CLA 0018)
    This album consists of 4 discs with 1 side each. All discs include Double Concerto in A Minor for Violin, Cello and Orchestra. The album is comprised of one-sided records. Records have white label with only the issue and matrix number on it.
  - Brahms: Sonata No. 3, in D Minor, Op. 108 (Record CAS CLA 0019)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes I: Allegro (Part 1). Side (B) includes IV: Presto agitato (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes I: Allegro (conc.). Side (B) includes IV: Presto agitato (Part 1).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes II: Adagio. Side (B) includes III: Un poco presto e con sentimento. Album also includes program notes inside album cover.
  - Brahms Symphony No. 4 in E Minor (Record CAS CLA 0020)
    This album consists of 5 discs, 4 of which have 2 sides. Disc 1 has only 1 side which includes I. Allegro non troppo (Part 1).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes I. Allegro non troppo (Part 2). Side (B) includes IV. Allegro energico et passionato (conc.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes I. Allegro non troppo (conc.). Side (B) includes IV. Allegro energico et passionato (Part 2).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes II. Andante moderato (Part 1). Side (B) includes (A) III. Allegro giocoso (conc.) (B) IV. Allegro energico e passionato (Part 1).
    Disc 5 side (A) includes II. Andante moderato (conc.). Side (B) includes III. Allegro giocoso (Part 1). Album also includes program notes by Veinus, A. included in booklet.
  - Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, Op. 26 (Record CAS CLA 0021)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes 1. Allegro Moderato (Part 1). Side (B) includes 3. Finale: Allegro energico (conc.). The discs are in WRONG album entitled "Beethoven Concerto in D Major For Violin and Orchestra."
  - Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, Op. 26 (Record CAS CLA 0022)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes 1. Allegro Moderato (Part 1). Side (B) includes 3. Finale: Allegro energico (conc.). This album is a Duplicate of Rosemary Casey 0376-0377. In WRONG album entitled "Beethoven Concerto in D Major For Violin and Orchestra."
  - Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, Op. 26 (Record CAS CLA 0023)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes 1. Allegro Moderato (conc.). Side (B) includes 3. Finale: Allegro energico (Part 1). This album is in WRONG album entitled "Beethoven Concerto in D Major For Violin and Orchestra."
  - Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, Op. 26 (Record CAS CLA 0024)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes 2. Adagio (Part 1). Side (B) includes 2. Adagio (conc.). The album is also in WRONG album entitled "Beethoven Concerto in D Major For Violin and Orchestra."
  - Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, Op. 26 (Record CAS CLA 0025)
    This album consists of 1 disc with 2 sides. Side (A) includes 2. Adagio (Part 1). Side (B) includes 2. Adagio (conc.). This album is also a duplicate of Rosemary Casey 0380-0381. Record is cracked. In WRONG album entitled "Beethoven Concerto in D Major For Violin and Orchestra"
  - Bruch Scottish Fantasy, Op. 46 (Record CAS CLA 0026)
    This album consists of 3 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes I. Introduction; Adagio cantabile (Part 1). Side (B) includes IV. Allegro guerriero (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes I. Adagio cantabile (conc.). Side (B) includes (A) III. Andante Sostenuto (conc.) (B) IV. Finale; Allegro guerriero.
    Disc 3 side (A) includes (A) II. Allegro; Adagio (conc.) (B) III. Andante sostenuto (Part 1). Side (B) includes III. Andante sostenuto (Part 2). The album also includes program notes inside cover.
  - Bruckner Symphony No. 7 in E Major (Record CAS CLA 0027)
    Scope amnd Content Notes
    This album consists of 6 discs with 2 sides each. Disc 1 side (A) includes I. Allegro Moderato (cont.). Side (B) includes 4. Finale: Bewegt, doch nicht schnell (conc.).
    Disc 2 side (A) includes I. Allegro Moderato (cont.). Side (B) includes 4. Finale: Bewegt, doch nicht schnell (cont.).
    Disc 3 side (A) includes I. Allegro Moderato (conc.). Side (B) includes 4. Finale: Bewegt, doch nicht schnell (beg.).
    Disc 4 side (A) includes 2. Adagio: Sehr feierlich und langsam (cont.). Side (B) includes 3. Scherzo: Sehr Schnell; Trio: Etwas langamer.
    Disc 5 side (A) includes 2. Adagio: Sehr feierlich und langsam (cont.). Side (B) includes 2. Adagio: Sehr feierlich und langsam (conc.).
    Disc 6 side (A) includes 2. Adagio: Sehr feierlich und langsam (cont.). Side (B) includes 2. Adagio: Sehr feierlich und langsam (cont.). Album also includes booklet with program notes. Set is missing first record and fifth record.